export const questions =[
    {
        id:1,
        question:'Q. What is AIF Trading Academy?',
        answer: 'AIF Trading Academy is an educational institution dedicated to providing high-quality training in stock market trading and investing. We offer a range of courses designed to empower individuals with the knowledge and skills needed to succeed in the financial markets.'
    },

    {
        id:2,
        question:'Q. Who can enroll in your courses?',
        answer: 'Our courses are open to anyone interested in learning about the stock market, regardless of their background or experience level. We offer courses suitable for beginners, intermediate traders, and advanced learners.'
    },

    {
        id:3,
        question:'Q. What topics do your courses cover?',
        answer: 'Our courses cover a wide range of topics, including technical analysis, fundamental analysis, options trading, intraday trading, long-term investing, portfolio management, and more. You can find detailed information about each course on our website.'
    },

    {
        id:4,
        question:'Q. How do I enroll in a course?',
        answer: 'To enroll in a course, visit our website and select the course you are interested in. Follow the enrollment instructions and you will be on your way to gaining valuable skills in stock market trading and investing.'
    },

    {
        id:5,
        question:'Q. Are there any prerequisites for your courses?',
        answer: 'Most of our courses do not have specific prerequisites, but some advanced courses may recommend prior knowledge of certain concepts. Please check the course descriptions for any prerequisites or recommended background knowledge.'
    },

    {
        id:6,
        question:'Q. What is your refund policy?',
        answer: 'Our refund policy varies depending on the course. Please refer to the specific course page on our website for details about the refund policy associated with that course.'
    },

    {
        id:7,
        question:'Q. Do you offer job placement services?',
        answer: 'Yes, we are proud to offer job placement services for our students. We have partnerships with financial firms and companies in related fields to help connect our students with job opportunities after completing our courses. '
        
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:'Q. How does your job placement service work?',
        answer: 'Our job placement services include resume assistance, interview preparation, and introductions to potential employers in the finance industry. We work closely with our students to match their skills and interests with suitable job openings.'
    },

    {
        id:9,
        question:'Q. Is job placement guaranteed?',
        answer: 'While we cannot guarantee job placement, we are committed to providing our students with the best possible support and opportunities. The success of our job placement services depends on various factors, including market conditions and individual effort.'
    },
    {
        id:10,
        question:'Q. How can I contact AIF Trading Academy for more information?',
        answer: 'You can reach out to us via email at (aiftradingacademy@gmail.com) or by using the contact form on our website. We are here to answer any questions you may have and assist you in your journey to becoming a successful trader or investor.'
    }
    
]